topseoinc.com 2013-02-06

# Privacy Policy « Top SEO Inc.

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy 

in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and make use 

of personal information. The following outlines our Privacy Policy. 

When accessing our Website, will learn certain information about 

you during your visit.

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology 

called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) 

and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information 

gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of 

visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited 

just before and just after our Web site, your IP address.

**What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique 

identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer 

for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically 

designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser 

if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser 

only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not 

the cookies sent to you by other sites.

**IP Addresses**

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the 

Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network 

to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web 

server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” 

so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

**Email Information**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content 

of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We 

provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ 

in the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone.

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering 

our business activities, providing customer service and making available other 

items and services to our customers and prospective customers.

will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you 

visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will 

such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties 

without the approval of the user at the time of collection.

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, 

when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection 

of our legal rights.

**A Special Note About Children**

Children are not eligible to use our web site and services and we ask that 

minors (under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us. If 

you are a minor, you can use this site only in conjunction with permission and 

guidance from your parents or guardians.

**How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?**

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, 

we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However, 

doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enter 

on our Web site may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure 

Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit Card information is never transmitted via email.

may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used 

for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections 

of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical 

design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available 

to all users, uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify 

unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

**Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without 

notice. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the 

future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under 

this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy 

Policy, without your prior consent.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles 

in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected 

and maintained. 

**Contact**

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, or your dealings with our 

web site, please contact us.
